<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-01-02T16:23:14-05:00</updated><id>srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">The Rang Blog</title><subtitle>It's a blog</subtitle><author><name>Sam Rang</name></author><entry><title type="html">Week 10 - GOTW: Cardinals - Bills</title><link href="srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/football/2020/11/19/GOTW-10-Cardinals-Bills.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Week 10 - GOTW: Cardinals - Bills" /><published>2020-11-19T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-11-19T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/football/2020/11/19/GOTW-10-Cardinals-Bills</id><content type="html" xml:base="srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/football/2020/11/19/GOTW-10-Cardinals-Bills.html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;game-of-the-week&quot;&gt;Game of the Week&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is now the fourth week in a row that we’ve had a bird-team in the GOTW and
the second week in a row that it’s been Kyler Murray’s bird-team. And make no
mistake, this is his team. He is eighth in the league in rushing (not just
quarterbacks), sixth in passing yards, ninth in completion percentage, and
eighth in passing TDs. He is objectively a star and only in his second year.
The biggest thing holding back this Cardinals team is the penalties. They lead
the league in both the number of penalties and total penalty yards (interestingly
enough they also lead the league in the number of penalties called in their favor).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first half of this game was a kicker’s fever dream with six field goals.
That said, all field goals are not created equal. The Bills’ defense had two
monster defensive stands inside the 10-yard line, after letting the Cardinals
drive the ball over 70 yards. Those drives resulted in Zane Gonzalez layups. On
the other side of the ball, the Bills had a sixth-round draft pick out of
Georgia Southern kicking personal bests &lt;em&gt;THREE TIMES&lt;/em&gt; in just the first half.
Tyler Bass started his day with a 54-, then a 55-, and then nailing a
(!!) 59-yarder right before halftime. The biggest takeaway from this first half
(besides being happy for Bass) is the lack of aggression from Klif. They kicked
field goals from the 3- and the 5-yard lines with the aforementioned stellar
Kyler Murray sitting on the sideline! Between that and all the penalties, there
is plenty of room for improvement. &lt;em&gt;&amp;lt;/vent&amp;gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The third quarter saw the Bills pull ahead, and then let the Cardinals back
into this game. After a handful of punts (including a 12 yarder) and each
team failing to turn interceptions into points, the real game started. With
about three and a half minutes on the clock, the Bills got the ball back after
a bad interception on the previous drive trailing by three. Josh Allen did a
great job of efficiently moving the ball and not giving up the big negative
plays (he had a great stiff arm/throwaway early in the drive), and was helped
out by Cole Beasley who had a highlight-reel one-handed catch as well as a key
2nd-and-13 conversion. Once they got inside field goal range, the Bills started
getting very careful about the clock, getting out of bounds and burning a
timeout, until all of a sudden Josh Allen delivers a 21-yard touchdown strike
to Stefon Diggs to - by all appearances - win the game. Stefon got to bask in
the limelight, high-fiving all of his teammates and explaining that was why he
came to Buffalo… HOWEVA there were still 34 seconds on the clock…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead of working the sidelines from the get-go, Kyler connected on a few
passes underneath, which moved them into the Bills side of the field but also
burned their remaining timeouts. Then with 21 seconds on the clock, Kyler wasted
10 seconds searching downfield for what amounted to a short dump off to Larry
Fitzgerald, who wisely got out of bounds after picking up the first down. That
left 11 seconds just inside the 45-yard line. Enough for one or two throws at
the endzone. He only needed one. Getting flushed from the pocket, Murray
scrambled left, slipped a defender, and then uncorked a deep shot into the end
zone. Somehow, someway, Deandre Hopkins (who is only 6’1”) levitated over the
three surrounding defenders to come down with the “hail Murray” pass. Cardinals
win (as does &lt;a href=&quot;https://arizonasports.com/story/2454035/cardinals-hopkins-wont-see-any-of-5-7-million-in-jordan-brand-exposure/&quot;&gt;Jordan Brand&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>srang</name></author><category term="football" /><category term="football" /><category term="game of the week" /><category term="cardinals" /><category term="bills" /><summary type="html">Game of the Week</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Week 6 - GOTW: Texans - Titans</title><link href="srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/football/2020/10/22/GOTW-6-Texans-Titans.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Week 6 - GOTW: Texans - Titans" /><published>2020-10-22T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-10-22T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/football/2020/10/22/GOTW-6-Texans-Titans</id><content type="html" xml:base="srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/football/2020/10/22/GOTW-6-Texans-Titans.html">&lt;p&gt;The Titans entered the game as one of three unbeaten teams in the NFL, while
the Texans were riding the post-B.O’B. hype-wave with a win over the
&lt;em&gt;juggernaut&lt;/em&gt; Jaguars. The Titans proved on TuNF that they were still firing on
all cylinders despite their COVID hiatus, and they came out strong again this
week. They put up touchdowns on long demoralizing possessions on three of
their first four drives and went into halftime up 21-10. Derrick Henry looked
like a man among children blasting through the Texans defense who ranks in the
bottom quarter of the league in DVOA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The third quarter, however, saw the Titans crumble like dried-out pumpkin
bread. The Texans scored 13 unanswered points while the Titans had a blocked
field goal, a lost fumble, and a missed field goal on consecutive drives.
&lt;em&gt;HOWEVA&lt;/em&gt;, both of the Texans’ touchdowns came on great field position, and
Tannehill still had shining moments mixed in, and while Henry completely
disappeared, only rushing for 14 yards in the quarter, you can never count him
out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the first play of Titans’ first drive of the 4th, down by two on their
own 6-yard line, Derrick Henry broke off a NINETY-FOUR (94) yard touchdown run
where he proved he’s not only stronger than the entire Texans team but also
faster. And then they put salt in the wound with a two-point conversion. (This
is also when Scoragami started getting interesting, jumping to 16%). Instead of
rolling over, Deshaun Watson led the Texans on a two-play 75-yard TD drive.
&lt;em&gt;And then&lt;/em&gt; the defense that had just been embarrassed 3 plays earlier picked
off a Tannehill deep ball, leading to a punishing 15-play, 7-minute touchdown
drive to put the Texans up by 7. And then something weird happened. Instead of
kicking the PAT to go up by 8, which would require the Titans to get a TD and
two-point conversion, the Texans went for 2 and failed to convert. Now,
Fairbairn did miss one extra point earlier in the game, and if they’d been able
to go up by 9 that would have completely iced the game but it still feels like
Romeo Crennel was daring fate with this one… and the Titans rose to the
challenge. Driving 76 yards down the field, the Titans tied the game with only
7 ticks on the clock. ONTO OVERTIME (this is also where we lost Scoragami
:disappointed:, it got to 87% which was thrilling).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Showing his versatility and maybe still feeling the sting of the third quarter,
Derrick Henry turned a 2nd-and-long screen pass into a 53-yard gain and took
the game into his presumably ginormous hands, and blasted a 3rd-and-goal
direct-snap in for a touchdown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Titans front office looks prophetic in running this team back from last year
with Tannehill at #4 in the Week 7 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nfl.com/news/qb-index-week-7-change-at-no-1-tom-brady-rises-into-top-10&quot;&gt;NFL QB
index&lt;/a&gt;
(we are praying for you &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/chriswesseling&quot;&gt;@ChrisWesseling&lt;/a&gt;),
throwing for 366 yards, 4 TDs, and only 1 INT, combined with Henry showing
plenty of tread left on his tires with over 250 yards of offense and two TDs of
his own. Titans play the only other undefeated AFC team later this week.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>srang</name></author><category term="football" /><category term="football" /><category term="game of the week" /><category term="titans" /><category term="texans" /><summary type="html">The Titans entered the game as one of three unbeaten teams in the NFL, while the Texans were riding the post-B.O’B. hype-wave with a win over the juggernaut Jaguars. The Titans proved on TuNF that they were still firing on all cylinders despite their COVID hiatus, and they came out strong again this week. They put up touchdowns on long demoralizing possessions on three of their first four drives and went into halftime up 21-10. Derrick Henry looked like a man among children blasting through the Texans defense who ranks in the bottom quarter of the league in DVOA.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Week 6 - Week in Review</title><link href="srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/football/2020/10/22/week6-review.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Week 6 - Week in Review" /><published>2020-10-22T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-10-22T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/football/2020/10/22/week6-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/football/2020/10/22/week6-review.html">&lt;p&gt;Week 6 is now behind us, which means that we are almost halfway through the
fantasy regular season (time flies when you’re having fun)! There were a lot of
interesting games this week:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We were 1:50 from a Scoragami in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/NFL_Scorigami/status/1317917295101026305?s=20&quot;&gt;Texans-Titans game&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;An NFC East team won a game (and it was a NY team!!)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Falcons didn’t blow a lead&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adam Gase, Doug Marone, Matt Patricia are all still NFL head coaches (at time of writing)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I watched the Detroit game, but literally couldn’t come up with a hot take, and I’m not sure if I’m sorry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>srang</name></author><category term="football" /><category term="football" /><category term="week in review" /><summary type="html">Week 6 is now behind us, which means that we are almost halfway through the fantasy regular season (time flies when you’re having fun)! There were a lot of interesting games this week:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Week 5 - GOTW: Seahawks - Vikings</title><link href="srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/football/2020/10/15/GOTW-5-Seahawks-Vikings.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Week 5 - GOTW: Seahawks - Vikings" /><published>2020-10-15T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-10-15T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/football/2020/10/15/GOTW-5-Seahawks-Vikings</id><content type="html" xml:base="srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/football/2020/10/15/GOTW-5-Seahawks-Vikings.html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;intro&quot;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New series this week! Introducing the Game of the Week (GOTW). It gives me a
chance to get a little deeper on a particular game each week (picked relatively
arbitrarily).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;game-of-the-week&quot;&gt;Game of the Week&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first half of this game was a little tough to watch. The Seahawks couldn’t
get anything going, punting on their 3 first-half possessions. The Vikings
leaned into the idea that the best defense is a good offense (plus a decent
defense) and put up points on three of their four first-half possessions,
mostly by feeding Dalvin Cook the ball and playing efficient ball-control
offense. Which was pretty boring. They had the ball for over 20 minutes of the
first half with only a single touchdown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then the second half happened. Dalvin Cook got injured on the first Vikings
play of the second half, which led to the wheels falling off the Vikings bus.
Minnesota’s first three second-half drives went like this: 3-and-out, Cousins
fumble, Cousins interception. Both turnovers (which were back-to-back
offensive plays), turned immediately into TDs for Seattle. TL;DR, 4 plays, 2
Viking turnovers, 2 Seahawk touchdowns. It’s safe to assume that Kirk Cousins
did not, in fact, like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://media.giphy.com/media/3oriNSH0Ddh93oO7PW/giphy.gif&quot; alt=&quot;You like that?&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trailing by 6 with two straight turnovers, this game was on the verge of
turning into a bloodbath, but Minnesota rallied late. Showing some
determination, they went back to the run game, leaning on Mattison in place of
the injured Cook, and scored on back-to-back touchdowns over 12 minutes of
possession time, covering 164 yards. After a 4th quarter interception, it
looked like they might even be able to put the game on ice. Unfortunately,
failing to convert on fourth down at the 6-yard line, the Vikings turned the
ball over up by five at the two-minute warning. Two minutes is too much for
Russell &amp;amp; Co. The real cook (pun intended) of this game put together a
gorgeous 1:42 minute, 94-yard drive ending in a touchdown to DK Metcalf to put
the Seahawks up by one. Seahawks win, Russ for MVP.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>srang</name></author><category term="football" /><category term="football" /><category term="game of the week" /><category term="seahawks" /><category term="vikings" /><summary type="html">Intro</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Week 4 - Week in Review</title><link href="srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/football/2020/10/08/week4-review.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Week 4 - Week in Review" /><published>2020-10-08T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-10-08T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/football/2020/10/08/week4-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/football/2020/10/08/week4-review.html">&lt;p&gt;We have passed the quarter pole on the season and we had a great slate of games
this week!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;BENGALS WIN!!!&lt;/em&gt; Three touchdowns and 151 yards from Joe Mixon after being
&lt;em&gt;HOSPITALIZED&lt;/em&gt; :dizzy_face: the night before with a chest injury. The Bengals
were able to get up by two scores late in the second half and after 3 weeks
of close games, they finally figured out how to control the clock on both sides
of the ball. This breaks their streak of losing one-score games and is the
longest stretch of unbeaten games in the Zac Taylor Era (they didn’t lose last
week!). Is Jacksonville tanking for Trevor? Who knows, but they are looking a
lot closer to the team we expected them to be this off-season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;:rotating_light: &lt;em&gt;COVID ALERT! COVID ALERT!&lt;/em&gt; :rotating_light:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had our first major pandemic-related disruption this week. Not only did the
matchup between the Steelers and Titans get moved to Week 7, but a very late
positive test of Cam Newton pushed yet another
way-too-early-AFC-powerhouse-matchup (Chiefs-Patriots) to Monday night. The
game ended up being a defensive chess-match (really, &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; low scoring).
After a 3-6 halftime score, each team scored an offensive touchdown in the
third quarter, but the real difference here was the Chiefs’ defense winning the
turnover battle with a pick &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; a pick-six in the fourth quarter (plus
another interception and fumble recovery earlier in the game). Chiefs win
26-10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tampa barely edged out LA in a shootout. With 20 years separating the ages of
the two starting quarterbacks, Herbert showed his mettle in his 3rd straight
start after LA lost Tyrod Taylor to a punctured lung. It looked like the
Chargers were going to run away with this game, going up 24-7, with the ball in
the last 30 seconds of the half. Unfortunately, they fumbled, allowing TB12
(Tompa Brady?) to find Mike Evans in the endzone right before halftime. The
second half was a showcase of stellar QB play but Tampa Bay got the win,
ending the game with an interception in the final three minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Browns gave Dallas the business for about two-and-a-half quarters on
Sunday, with 2 rushing touchdowns, and another two through the air including a
gadget play with Landry throwing a 37-yard laser to OBJ. HOWEVA, the domination
came to a screeching halt in the third quarter, when all of a sudden the Browns
offense evaporated, letting Dallas score 24 unanswered points including
THREE two-point conversions. Dak put up 502 yards and 4 touchdowns this week,
becoming the first player in NFL history to throw for 450+ yards in three
straight games, but even that wasn’t enough. This game had some crazy fun in
the last few minutes including a recovered blocked extra point by the Browns
and an interception to ice the game. Browns win 49-38.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Josh Allen had a shoulder injury scare (but didn’t technically miss a play). In
more relevant news, his facial hair game is actually worse than mine (who knew
such a thing was possible). Oh, and Bills are a legit 4-0 team; protect your
folding tables and condiments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Eagles came into the SNF tilt winless, but after upsetting the 49ers in
SF, they left atop the NFC East standings (yes that division is a
dumpster fire).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Football Czar Bill O’Brien gets the boot from Houston after an 0-4 start
including a loss to the previously winless and seemingly hopeless Vikings. Who
would have thought that B.O.B. would get the boot before Adam Gase?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>srang</name></author><category term="football" /><category term="football" /><category term="week in review" /><summary type="html">We have passed the quarter pole on the season and we had a great slate of games this week!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Week 3 - Week in Review</title><link href="srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/football/2020/10/01/week3-review.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Week 3 - Week in Review" /><published>2020-10-01T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-10-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/football/2020/10/01/week3-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/football/2020/10/01/week3-review.html">&lt;p&gt;Another week is in the books! We’ve had some surprise contenders emerge and
some off-season hopefuls turn into disappointments, it almost feels like a
normal football season!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It might not have been as good as the Battle of Ohio, but The Beard vs. The
Stache (and/or battle for East Coast of Florida…) was still fun. Minshew has
emerged this season as a surprisingly viable starting quarterback, and in this
Week 3 matchup, he out-distanced Fitz 246 to 156 in air yards but went
0-3 on fourth down conversions. Meanwhile, the Old Man and the Sea brought his
Fitz-&lt;i&gt;magic&lt;/i&gt; to bear early with three touchdowns on their first three drives.
Miami wins 31-13.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Bengals managed to find something more dissatisfying than a loss, tying the
Eagles 23-23. These are the same Eagles whose stadium-sound-team piped in
booing last week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Bears are the latest team to emerge like a phoenix from yet another Falcons
fourth quarter flame out. The Falcons gave up a 16 point lead in the fourth
quarter after the Bears benched Trubisky for Foles, and somehow the Bears are
3-0 on the season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gostkowski has redeemed himself from his 1-4 kicking performance in Week 1,
going 6 for 6 this week with kicks from 30, 31, 39, 51, 54, and 55 (!). Titans
seem to be having a surprising amount of success running things back from last
year, moving to 3-0 on the season, while Minnesota has lots of questions to
answer, sitting at 0-3.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both New York teams STINK. That is all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seahawks and Packers are both rolling through their opponents this season, led
by their quarterbacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MNF was a matchup that came too early in the season but wasn’t as close as we
all hoped. Mahomes cooked, Ravens couldn’t keep up.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>srang</name></author><category term="football" /><category term="football" /><category term="week in review" /><summary type="html">Another week is in the books! We’ve had some surprise contenders emerge and some off-season hopefuls turn into disappointments, it almost feels like a normal football season!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Week 2 - Week in Review</title><link href="srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/football/2020/09/21/week2-review.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Week 2 - Week in Review" /><published>2020-09-21T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-09-21T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/football/2020/09/21/week2-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/football/2020/09/21/week2-review.html">&lt;p&gt;Wow, what a week! Before covering anything else, we should address the elephant
in the room, Thursday Night Football. I think we can all agree that the history
here is important. Nearly 25 years of experience, a multi-sport professional
career including a same-day-multi-sport-double-header, and he’s even called a
game with Obama. I think we can all agree that Joe Buck will look great in a
gold jacket, not to mention he won’t be able to rib Troy Aikman quite so much
for his Hall of Fame status. I didn’t really pay attention to the game though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The lack of preseason has reared its ugly head at knees and ankles this week:
Saquon Barkley (ACL), Nick Bosa (ACL), Cortland Sutton (ACL,MCL), Marlon Mack
(Achilles), C.J. Uzomah (Achilles) are all likely out for the season, then
George Kittle (sprained knee), Julio Jones (hamstring), Drew Lock (sprained
shoulder), Davante Adams (hamstring), Michael Thomas (high ankle sprain),
Phillip Lindsay (sprained toe), Le’Veon Bell (hamstring), Parris Campbell
(MCL,PCL), Christian McCaffrey (ankle), Chris Godwin (concussion), Kenny
Golladay (hamstring), and Tyrod Taylor (chest) all missed time this week with
various ailments. The 49ers, in particular, were gutted: in addition to Kittle
and Bosa, Jimmy Garoppolo suffered a high ankle sprain, Raheem Mostert sprained
his MCL, and Solomon Thomas tore his ACL as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doom and gloom aside, there was still some great football on TV… unless you
are a Falcons fan, in which case, it may be time for some self-reflection.
After falling behind 0-20 with three fumbles, the Cowboys put together an
amazing 11-play drive for a Zeke TD run to close out the first quarter. Then,
after a flurry of scores back and forth including three rushing touchdowns by
Prescott, the Cowboys successfully converted a crazy spinny onside kick in the
final two minutes and drove the ball down for a game-winning 46-yard field
goal, beating the Falcons 40-39. Before this game, teams that scored 39
points with 0 turnovers were 440-0, now 440-1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In place of hospitalized Tyrod Taylor (whose lung was punctured in a pre-game
procedure :scream:), Justin Herbert planted his flag, becoming the
first player to score a rushing and passing touchdown in the first half of his
debut game since 1954. He led the Chargers against AFC West rival and defending
Super Bowl Champions - the Kansas City Chiefs - and took them to overtime, but
the brewing upset was eventually foiled by Harrison Butker, who nailed a
58-yarder (after having a 53-yarder wiped by a penalty and another 58-yarder
wiped by timeout).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The SNF matchup this weekend turned out to be everything anyone could
have hoped for. Looking like yet another Bill Belichick fever dream, down 5 the
Patriots put together an 80-yard drive leading to a first-and-goal at the
1-yard line with 3 seconds on the clock and Cam Newton under center. &lt;em&gt;PLOT TWIST&lt;/em&gt;!
Cam tackled for a loss, time expires, Seahawks win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no Autumn Wind in the new Las Vegas Raiders stadium, but they still
blew over the Saints in their first home game. With a punishing run attack,
Gruden’s team is getting to play some old-school football in a brand new home,
and at 2-0, it seems like all the off-season questions about the Raiders’ QB
have evaporated in the Nevada desert heat.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>srang</name></author><category term="football" /><category term="football" /><category term="week in review" /><summary type="html">Wow, what a week! Before covering anything else, we should address the elephant in the room, Thursday Night Football. I think we can all agree that the history here is important. Nearly 25 years of experience, a multi-sport professional career including a same-day-multi-sport-double-header, and he’s even called a game with Obama. I think we can all agree that Joe Buck will look great in a gold jacket, not to mention he won’t be able to rib Troy Aikman quite so much for his Hall of Fame status. I didn’t really pay attention to the game though.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Week 1 - Week in Review</title><link href="srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/football/2020/09/15/week1-review.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Week 1 - Week in Review" /><published>2020-09-15T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-09-15T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/football/2020/09/15/week1-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/football/2020/09/15/week1-review.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Football is BACK!&lt;/em&gt; And it was glorious. Let’s just bask for a minute in
professional football being on TV again, in no particular order:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Browns are still bad but maybe Cody Parkey will solve their problems?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The WFT shocked the world by being good&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Patriots shocked no one by being good&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Bengals shocked &lt;em&gt;only&lt;/em&gt; me by being bad (trending towards average… ONE OPI from a win)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Jaguars proved that you don’t have to be good to win&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Bears have now won five straight matchups against Detroit, and the Trubisky legacy lives on!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Old QBs can still ball&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Jerry Jones is jealous of the Ram’s new stadium&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It took until Tuesday morning before I noticed that the Cardinals actually won the game against
 the defending NFC champs. So much for the 49er’s running things back&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>srang</name></author><category term="football" /><category term="football" /><category term="week in review" /><summary type="html">Football is BACK! And it was glorious. Let’s just bask for a minute in professional football being on TV again, in no particular order:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome to the Rang Blog!</title><link href="srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/general/2020/09/01/welcome.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to the Rang Blog!" /><published>2020-09-01T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-09-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/general/2020/09/01/welcome</id><content type="html" xml:base="srang.github.io/samuelrang.com/general/2020/09/01/welcome.html">&lt;p&gt;Somehow, some way, you’ve found yourself on my blog. It’s part side project,
part fun (those aren’t mutually exclusive).  I’ll be writing about all sorts of
things from what’s going on in the NFL, favorite games and movies, to how I
built this site and vim plugins. Hopefully this is either fun or helpful for
you as well!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;testing&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>srang</name></author><category term="general" /><category term="updates" /><category term="general" /><summary type="html">Somehow, some way, you’ve found yourself on my blog. It’s part side project, part fun (those aren’t mutually exclusive). I’ll be writing about all sorts of things from what’s going on in the NFL, favorite games and movies, to how I built this site and vim plugins. Hopefully this is either fun or helpful for you as well!</summary></entry></feed>